

# **ABOUT ME**

Informatics Engineer, he is creative, committed and with high attention to detail. He has about 3 years of experience in software development, such as web development and UI/UX fundamentals. He has recently received awards in the company where he is currently working, for his work attitude, work results and innovation in software solutions. He has an advanced level of English, and he is certified in SCRUM and agile methods.

#### CONTACT

Phone: +57 (300)-3805184 Email: santiriva19@gmail.com

Portfolio: https://santiagorivadeneira.com

Linkedin: Visit my profile

# **EDUCATION**

#### Universidad de la Sabana

Master in Applied Analytics, 2023/1 - Present

• 30% Scholaship for the whole Master

# Universidad de la Sabana

Informatics Engineer, 2018 - 2023

- Member of the football team and represents the university in regional championships.
- Certified in scrum and agile methods
- Graduated with 4.2/5 GPA

# SANTIAGO RIVADENEIRA DELGADO

# **FULLSTACK DEVELOPER**

# **WORK HISTORY**

# **Intermediate React Developer**

Unosquare SAS, February 2023, Present

 He was hired to build effective, efficient and reliable code implementing great practices in React js, React Native and Node.js.

# Full-stack developer

Howdy, Dec 2021 - February 2023

- He currently uses mainly Javascript for developing web pages, using the framework React Js for the frontend and Node JS for the backend.
- He participates in all the SCRUM events of the development team.
- He is a part of a development team conformed by around 80 developers around the globe.
- He currently combines his work responsibilities with his university and with the soccer practices. Which has gave him even more discipline than before.
- He has been developing a chrome extension to scrap information from Google Flights website.

#### **Software Developer**

Teleperformance SAS, Nov 2020 - Dec 2021

- He used Javascript for developing web pages, using the framework React Js for the frontend and Node JS for the backend.
- He was hired to use RPA (Robot Process Automation)
- He was also the main designer and frontend developer of the development team.

# Colegio Para Hijos de empleados de la Contraloría General de la República

High-school, 2017

- · Graduado con honores académicos
- Vicepresidente del Club de Matemática, 2012

# Alonzo And Tracy Mourning (Miami)

High-school, 2015

• Attended 9th grade in Miami to learn english.

# Norman S. Edelpcurp (Miami)

Middle-school, 2013

• Attended 6th grade in Miami to learn english

# **Fullstack Developer**

Consorcio Delgado Murcia, Jun 2020 - Nov 2020

- Built, developed and implemented a web page responsive and fully informative.
- Responsible of developing the designing the product (frontend) using mockup tools such as Photoshop and Adobe XD.

# Frontend developer

Terra Engineering, Jan 2020 - Jun 2020

- Built, developed and implemented a web page responsive and fully informative.
- Responsible of developing the designing the product (frontend) using mockup tools such as Photoshop and Adobe XD.

# **KNOWLEDGE**



# **RELEVANT COURSES AND CERTIFICATIONS**

# Curso de Desarrollo de Apps para iOS

Platzi, jun 2022

# Curso Básico de GraphQL

Platzi, dec 2021

#### **Unit Testing con Jest en React**

Platzi, Dec 2021

# Node.js: Base de Datos con MongoDB y WebSockets

Platzi, Nov 2021

# **Curso de Webpack**

Platzi, sept 2022

# **React Native Complete Course**

Udemy, Nov 2020

# **Agile Methods Concepts**

University of La Sabana, May 2020

#### **Scrum Foundations Professional Certificate**

Udemy, Juli 2021